firstusa.com 2001-10-21

# Privacy Policy

|  |   
---|---  
  |    
**_Privacy Policy_**  
| privacy policy  
| online practices  
| questions about privacy  
| security information  
| terms of use  
|  |  |   
privacy  policy  
---  
   
| Consumer Information Values and Privacy Policy  
|  Our Consumer Information Values and Privacy Policy is provided to help you understand how we protect your financial privacy, just as we protect your financial assets.  This policy provides you with an opportunity to make informed choices about the management of personal information.  Also, there are several convenient ways to obtain more information, including answers to commonly asked questions about privacy.  You may call us toll-free at 1-800-869-9638 or visit one of Bank One’s three major websites: [www.bankone.com](http://www.bankone.com/), [www.FirstUSA.com](http://www.firstusa.com/), and [www.WingspanBank.com](http://www.wingspanbank.com/). This Policy is provided to you jointly by the Bank One companies listed at the end of this Policy.  The Bank One family includes many companies and banks; some are identified with the Bank One name, and some are not—for example: Bank One, Kentucky, NA, Banc One Financial Services, Midwest Mortgage Services, WingspanBank.com, and First USA Bank, NA.ValuesFour key values form the foundation of our Privacy Policy:  
|  **Information security is a priority.**

One of our highest priorities is information security.  We regularly review our security standards and practices to protect against unauthorized disclosure of information.

**Privacy is a shared responsibility.**

You trust us to care for your financial needs, and you have a right to feel confident that we are responsibly managing your account and information about you.  At the same time, there are things you can do to help protect your privacy, such as knowing what information is on your credit report, understanding the choices you have about the use of your information, and protecting your passwords.

**Responsible use of information is beneficial.**

Information is important for meeting your needs and providing consistent service quality.  Information is also the source of new ideas.  The more we understand about you, the better we can suggest products and services, create new opportunities for you, and help you manage your financial assets.

**Information flow and privacy are a balance.**

We must meet expectations for privacy while still managing information to conduct our business and serve you.  Information must be shared to fulfill your requests, deliver products and services, administer and update accounts, reduce fraud and other risks, and to comply with laws and regulations.   
  
| PolicyOne Policy on the Collection, Use, and Sharing of Personal InformationBank One has one Privacy Policy for consumers that applies to all of the Bank One family.  One Privacy Policy makes it easy to understand and convenient for people to make informed choices about the management of personal information.Information Covered by this PolicyOur Policy applies to all personally identifiable financial information about you that is obtained by Bank One in connection with providing a consumer financial product or service for personal, family, or household purposes ("personal information").  Our Policy will continue to cover information we may collect about you during the course of our relationship as well as after the relationship has ended.How We Collect Personal InformationWe rely on many sources of information to understand and meet your needs.  We collect personal information about you from:

  * your applications or in other ways when you visit us in person, over the phone, through the mail or through our websites;
  * your browser, when you visit our websites and your browser interacts with us;
  * your transactions with any of the companies in the Bank One family;
  * consumer reporting agencies; and
  * other sources, in connection with providing you a financial product or service.

How We Keep Information SecureInformation security is one of our highest priorities.  This priority is emphasized by our internal employee Code of Conduct, this Privacy Policy, and the contracts and agreements that we sign with external suppliers and partners.  Employees who violate our policies and procedures regarding privacy are subject to disciplinary action, and our partners and suppliers are bound to uphold our procedures regarding privacy under the terms of our legal contracts with them.  We safeguard information by regularly assessing security standards and procedures to protect against unauthorized access to personal information.

We limit access to personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products and services to you.  We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your personal information.

Information Sharing Within the Bank One Family and Your Opportunity to “Opt Out”People often tell us that they prefer a financial services provider that takes an “integrated approach.”  They want us to understand a range of needs and make recommendations about a variety of financial services.  For this reason and others, we may share any of the personal information that we collect about you among companies within the Bank One family.

The Fair Credit Reporting Act gives you the opportunity to limit the sharing of “non- experience information” within the Bank One family.  “Non-experience information” includes information that is used, expected to be used, or collected for the purpose of establishing your eligibility for consumer credit, insurance or deposit accounts, and is not related solely to your transactions or other experiences with us, including information:

  * from your applications, such as your income or marital status;
  * from a credit report, such as your credit history; and
  * from sources used to verify representations made by you, such as your open lines of credit or employment history.

The types of companies within the Bank One family that may receive non- experience information include financial service providers, such as:
  * banks;
  * broker-dealers; and
  * insurance agents.

**If you prefer that we not share non-experience information about you within the Bank One family of companies, you may opt out, that is, you may direct us not to share this information, by calling us toll-free at 1-800-869-9638.**

If you choose to opt out of the sharing of this information within the Bank One family, we will not share non-experience information about you for any accounts or loans that you may have with us.  For any accounts or loans that you hold jointly with another person, each person may separately opt out and joint account holders may opt out for each other.  If only one joint account holder opts out, we may share information about the other joint account holders.  Choosing to opt out of this information sharing may limit opportunities for you to receive product and service information that may interest you.

**Information Sharing Outside the Bank One Family and Your Opportunity to “Opt Out”**

We may share any of the personal information that we collect about you with companies or other organizations outside of the Bank One family, including:

  * financial service providers, such as mortgage bankers, securities broker-dealers and insurance agents;
  * non-financial companies, such as retailers, direct marketers, membership clubs and publishers; and
  * other companies and organizations, such as non-profit organizations.

**If you prefer that we not share personal information about you with companies and organizations outside the Bank One family (except information described below under “Other Information Sharing”), you may opt out, that is, you may direct us not to share this information, by calling us toll-free at 1-800-869-9638.**

If you choose to opt out of the sharing of personal information with companies and organizations outside the Bank One family, we will not share any personal information about you for any accounts or loans that you may have with us.  For any accounts or loans that you hold jointly with another person, each person may separately opt out and joint account holders may opt out for each other.  If only one joint account holder opts out, we may share information about the other joint account holders.  Choosing to opt out of this information sharing may limit opportunities for you to receive product and service information that may interest you.

Other Information SharingWe may also share personal information about you with companies or other organizations outside of the Bank One family as required by or permitted by law.  For example, we may share personal information to:

  * protect against fraud;
  * respond to a subpoena; or
  * service your account.

In addition, Bank One may work with companies or organizations outside of the Bank One family to provide services to Bank One or to provide you with opportunities to buy products or services offered by Bank One or jointly with other financial institutions.  Consequently, we may disclose any of the personal information that we have collected about you to:
  * other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements; and
  * companies that perform services, including marketing services, for us or for us and the financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

For your protection, we require that these companies keep all personal information secure and confidential.Children’s Online Information PrivacyWe don’t knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from our websites about children under age 13.  If a child whom we know to be under age 13 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, notify parents, or seek parental consent.  We are not, however, responsible for the collection and use of information by companies or organizations outside of the Bank One family that may be linked to our websites.Bank One Companies Providing This NoticeThis policy is provided by the Bank One companies listed below.  Separate disclosures of additional information may be provided to you if required under applicable state law.

American National Bank and Trust Company of Chicago  
Banc One Acceptance Company  
Banc One Credit Company  
Banc One Financial Services, Inc.  
Banc One High Yield Partners, LLC  
Banc One Insurance Agency, Inc.  
Banc One Investment Advisors Corporation  
Banc One Kentucky Insurance Company  
Banc One Kentucky Leasing Corporation  
Banc One Realty Advisors, Inc.  
Banc One Securities Corporation  
Banc One Texas Leasing Corporation  
Bank One, Arizona, NA  
Bank One, Colorado, NA  
Bank One Exchange Corporation  
Bank One, Florida  
Bank One, Illinois, NA  
Bank One, Indiana, NA  
Bank One, Kentucky, NA  
Bank One, Louisiana, NA  
Bank One, Michigan  
Bank One, NA (Chicago, Illinois)  
Bank One, NA (Columbus, Ohio)  
Bank One, Oklahoma, NA  
Bank One, Texas, NA  
Bank One Trust Company, NA  
Bank One, Utah, NA  
Bank One, West Virginia, NA  
Bank One, Wheeling-Steubenville, NA  
Bank One, Wisconsin  
BOX Leasing Corporation  
Congress Life Insurance Company  
First Chicago NBD Mortgage Company  
First USA Bank, NA  
Midwest Mortgage Services  
WingspanBank.com  
Wingspan Investment Services, Inc.
